(Raj:)There it is, Priya.
We're Indian.
(Raj:)We believe this stuff.
(Priya:)I think it also says that
if you eat beef,
(Priya:)you need to live with cows
for three months
(Priya:)and drink their urine.
(Raj:)Some of it makes sense,
some of it's crazy.
(Raj:)My point is, you can't go out
with Leonard.
(Penny(arriving):)Who can't go out with Leonard?
(Raj:)My sister.
(Leonard:)Penny, this is
Raj's sister, Priya.
(Priya:)It's very nice to meet you.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, you, too.
(Sheldon:)Priya, if you're experiencing
any tension or awkwardness,
(Sheldon:)it may stem from the fact that
Leonard and Penny used to--
(Sheldon:)if I may quote Howard--
"do the dance with no pants."
(Penny:)Sheldon!
(Leonard:)Really?
(Howard:)Hey, Bernadette, can I
talk to you for a second?
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Raj:)Penny, you became disenchanted
with Leonard
(Raj:)as a lover.
(Raj:)Would you please tell
my sister why?
(Howard:)Listen, my mom's
going to Palm Springs
(Howard:)to visit her sister.
(Howard:)That's two whole nights
in a row I can sleep over